Nick Wesselmann

<u>Nick.Wesselmann@Mystic5523.com</u> | (913)579-7592 | Mission, KS <u>Linkedin.com/in/nick-wesselmann</u> | <u>Github.com/Mystic5523</u> | Website: www.Mystic5523.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Webdesigner with background in security. 12 years of experience in interacting with people, both in person and remotely. Duties include building and using databases to track information and running the switchboard for a national mutual fund company. Currently finishing a Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, GIT, Github, Firebase, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, Command Line, MS Word and Excel.

PROJECTS

- Uses multiple APIs to search for a recipe and uses the results to find a video
- Utilizes Bootstrap, Bootswatch, and some custom CSS for styles
- Utilizes the YouTube API for an embedded iFrame player.

EXPERIENCE

Security Officer Aug 2006 - Present

Allied Universal Security Services

- Level 5 Master Security Officer
 - CPR/AED Certified
 - First Aid Certified
 - Patrol and CCTV Camera Monitoring
 - Access Control
 - Management of Aggressive Behavior (MOAB Self Defence) Certified

Nutrition Services 2001 - Aug 2006

Shawnee Mission Medical Center

- Prepare and served meals to patients and employees
- Sanitation Duties

Volunteer Work

Camp Companion 2002 - 2009

Camp Quality Northwest Missouri

- Supervisor and Monitor children of all ages
- Set up and take down camp equipment

Shawnee Mission Medical Center Volunteer

1997 - 2001

Gift Shop - Food Pantry

- Sales and supply
- Responsible for tracking of sales and of inventory

EDUCATION

University of Kansas Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, & React Js.

Johnson County Community College

- Associates of Arts in Criminal Justice
- Vice President of Lambda Alpha Epsilon Criminal Justice Fraternity